<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on RFNL</title><link>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/</link><description>Recent content in Home on RFNL</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minetest in school</title><link>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2021-03-09-minetest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2021-03-09-minetest/</guid><description>We are starting a Minetest project at school!
After we have been dealing with the technology for a while (here good to follow up), we have now started the Minetest project in school. First in trial mode, we want to get to know how our infrastructure works and how the families cope with the connection to our server - after all we still have remote students and we want to detach this kind of offer a bit from the presence in school.</description></item><item><title>Roadmap 2021</title><link>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-12-21-roadmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-12-21-roadmap/</guid><description>Like every year, we come together at the end of the year to review the year and plan what to do next. Usually connected with a small Christmas party - this time of course by remote meeting. Not as cozy as usual, but still rich in content.
We have a lot of plans for 2021 - the financing of the high school has to be secured, as well as the funding for the further plans.</description></item><item><title>#EUvsVirus Hackathon - We are in!</title><link>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-04-23-euvsvirus/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2020 03:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-04-23-euvsvirus/</guid><description>We received the information about the EU Hackathon at very short notice, and it was clear right away - we&amp;rsquo;re in! Several 10,000 people from all over Europe meet online to implement smart ideas against the crisis. For millions of students, the school crisis that is currently looming is certainly crucial.
We want to start with an innovative app idea for students who want to invent, design and test their learning path themselves - alone and together with their mentor.</description></item><item><title>Our first Online-Meetup</title><link>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-04-07-our-first-meetup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 17:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://raum-fuer-natuerliches-lernen.de/en/work/2020-04-07-our-first-meetup/</guid><description>Very exciting today - our first Online-Meetup with 12 participants on the topic -how can good online cooperation succeed?- After a short introduction into the connection between our association, our school and the &amp;ldquo;online&amp;rdquo; topic, which is currently receiving a lot of attention due to the Covid 19 crisis and the school closures, an interesting exchange on the topic started.
Core learning: digital platforms can help us to bridge distance - the motivation and impulses for learning still come from the participants and their good relations with each other, not from conserved &amp;ldquo;content&amp;rdquo;.</description></item></channel></rss>